http://www.tekgalaxy.com/privacypolicy.cfm

Video Games
FREE SHIPPING ON OUR ENTIRE CATALOG!
Our Commitment to Privacy
Our Privacy Policy was developed as an extension of our commitment to combine
the highest-quality products and services with the highest level of integrity in
dealing with our clients and partners. The Policy is designed to assist you in
understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the personal information you
provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site
and our services. This statement will be continuously assessed against new
technologies, business practices and our customers' needs.
What Information Do We Collect?
When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information:
personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an
individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as
you and others browse our Web site.
1. Personal Information You Choose to Provide
Credit Card Information
If you choose to purchase products or services from our partners, or us you may
need to give personal information and authorization to obtain information from
various credit services. For example, you may need to provide the following
information:
· Home and business phone number
· Other personal information (i.e. mother's maiden name)
Email Information
In addition to providing the foregoing information to our partners, if you
choose to correspond further with us through email, we may retain the content of
your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We
provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ
in the maintenance of information received by mail and telephone.
2. Web Site Use Information
Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard
technology called "cookies" (see explanation below, "What Are
Cookies?") and Web server logs to collect information about how our Web
site is used. Information gathered through cookies and Web server logs may
include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web
site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This
information is collected on an aggregate basis. None of this information is
associated with you as an individual.
How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?
Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering our
business activities, providing customer service and making available other
products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally,
we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes
to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find
valuable. The lists used to send you product and service offers are developed
and managed under our traditional corporate standards designed to safeguard the
security and privacy of our customers' personal information. As a customer, you
will be given the opportunity, at least once annually, to notify us of your
desire not to receive these offers.
What Are Cookies? Cookies are a feature of Web browser software that allows
Web servers to recognize the computer used to access a Web site. Cookies are
small pieces of data that are stored by a user's Web browser on the user's hard
drive. Cookies can remember what information a user accesses on one Web page to
simplify subsequent interactions with that Web site by the same user or to use
the information to streamline the user's transactions on related Web pages. This
makes it easier for a user to move from Web page to Web page and to complete
commercial transactions over the Internet. Cookies should make your online
experience easier and more personalized.
How Do We Use Information We Collect from Cookies?
We use Web site browser software tools such as cookies and Web server logs to
gather information about our Web site users' browsing activities, in order to
constantly improve our Web site and better serve our customers. This information
assists us to design and arrange our Web pages in the user-friendliest manner
and to continually improve our Web site to better meet the needs of our
customers and prospective customers.
Cookies help us collect important business and technical statistics. The
information in the cookies lets us trace the paths followed by users to our Web
site as they move from one page to another. Web server logs allow us to count
how many people visit our Web site and evaluate our Web site's visitor capacity.
We do not use these technologies to capture your individual email address or any
personally identifying information about you although they do permit us to send
focused online banner advertisements or other such responses to you.
Sharing Information with Affiliates
From time to time you may notice offers from outside companies advertised on our
Web site. We take measures to select product or service providers that are
responsible and afford privacy protections to their customers. However, we
cannot make any representations about the practices and policies of these
companies.
Notice of New Services and Changes
Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about
important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you
will find valuable. As our client, you will be given the opportunity to notify
us of your desire not to receive these offers by clicking on a response box when
you receive such an offer.
How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?
When you send confidential personal credit card information to us on our Web
site, a secure server software which we have licensed encrypts all information
you input before it is sent to us. The information is scrambled en route and
decoded once it reaches our Web site.
Other email that you may send to us may not be secure unless we advise you
that security measures will be in place prior to your transmitting the
information. For that reason, we ask that you do not send confidential
information such as Social Security or account numbers to us through an
unsecured email.
How Do We Protect Your Information?
Information Security. We utilize encryption/security software to safeguard
the confidentiality of personal information we collect from unauthorized access
or disclosure and accidental loss, alteration or destruction.
Evaluation of Information Protection Practices. Periodically, our operations
and business practices are reviewed for compliance with corporate policies and
procedures governing the security, confidentiality and quality of our
information.
Employee Access, Training and Expectations. Our corporate values, ethical
standards, policies and practices are committed to the protection of customer
information. In general, our business practices limit employee access to
confidential information, and limit the use and disclosure of such information
to authorized persons, processes and transactions.
Do We Disclose Information to Outside Parties?
We may provide aggregate information about our customers, sales, Web site
traffic patterns and related Web site information to our affiliates or reputable
third parties, but this information will not include personally identifying
data, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy.
What About Legally Compelled Disclosure of Information?
We may disclose information when legally compelled to do so, in other words,
when we, in good faith, believe that the law requires it or for the protection
of our legal rights.
What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?
We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from
our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to
other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that
may be useful to the users of our Web site.
Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another
Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and
interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our
Web site, is subject to that Web site's own rules and policies. Please read over
those rules and policies before proceeding.
Your Consent
By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal
information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy
policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you
aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances
we may disclose it.
Sign up for Newsletter
...and receive great deals in your inbox.
Subscribe
unsubscribe
Shipping to the Milky Way Planets
As long as that planet has life as we know it, we will find a way to get it there. It obviously won't qualify for free shipping as jet fuel is pretty expensive. Also, we cannot gaurantee 3-day delivery as we are still working on breaking light speed here at TechnologyGalaxy.com
Find it Fast
Accessories
Cables
Cameras
Desktops
Monitors
Network
Notebooks
